Finding Aid for Mark Foster Collection 1967-1979
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Mark Foster Collection 1967-1979
Foster, Mark, collector.
1 linear ft.
Papers collected by Mark Foster of Ypsilanti, Michigan. Printed material relating to the founding and growth of the Catholic charismatic movement; also survey taken among Catholic students at the University of Michigan and Michigan State University.
85186 Aa 2
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Mark Foster (donor no. 6446 ) and came to the library in 1980.
The collection is open for research.
Maark Foster was a collector of materials relating to the Catholic charismatic movement.
The Mark Foster papers deal exclusively with the founding and growth of the Catholic charismatic movement. The material divides itself into two groups, a chronological sequence and opinion survey material. The chronological files, covering the years 1967 to 1979, consist primarily of printed material. While an occasional letter and a few obscure mimeographed publications can be found, most of the items are from available sources. The survey material consists of both summary data and individual questionnaires. The forms were circulated among students at the University of Michigan during the years 1967, 1968 and 1969, and to students at Michigan State University during 1969.
Subjects:
Catholic Church--Michigan.; Michigan State University--Religion.; Pentecostalism--Catholic Church.; University of Michigan--Religion.
- Chronological file
  - 1967, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1968 (Box 1)
  - 1969, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1970 (Box 1)
  - 1971, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1972 (Box 1)
  - 1973, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - 1974, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1975, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1976 (Box 1)
  - 1977 (Box 1)
  - 1978 (Box 1)
  - 1979 (Box 1)
- Catholic student surveys
  - University of Michigan
    - 1967 (Box 1)
    - 1968 (Box 1)
    - 1969 (Box 1)
  - Michigan State University
    - 1969 (Box 1)